iima.ac.in 2016-11-22

# Privacy Policy

                                              Privacy Policy
Privacy Statement
Thanks for visiting website of Indian Institute of Management, Ahmedabad (IIMA).
IIMA understands that the privacy of its users is important. Information collected on
http://www.iimahd.ernet.in/ is kept private and never shared with other organizations. We’re making
this privacy statement to inform you about the types of information gathered and disseminated on the
Website. Please note, that this policy has been developed with the recognition that Internet
technologies continue to develop and evolve rapidly, and that such changes may require us to alter
our Privacy Policy. Any such alterations will not affect our general commitment to the protection of our
visitors’ privacy.
General Statement
You may visit our website without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. However,
certain transactions that you choose to engage in on this site will require your submission of personal
information, including, but not limited to, profile updates, applications and certain databases. As a
general rule, IIMA will not sell, swap, rent, or otherwise disclose to any third party any such personal
information for commercial purposes. Such information will be utilized only for the purpose stated. To
accomplish such purpose, IIMA may disclose the information to its employees, consultants and
agents who have a legitimate need to know the information. IIMA also reserves the right to disclose
this information under special circumstances, including disclosures required by law, court order or
circumstances under which disclosure, in the sole discretion of IIMA, is necessary to protect the legal
rights, including the intellectual property rights, of IIMA.
Use of Information
IIMA may collect other information about its users that is not connected with any specific personal
identity, such as data about usage and service operation. The following summarizes the types of
information that we may collect.
System Information, IP Addresses and Referrers
When you connect to our website, our web server may record the numerical Internet Protocol (IP)
address of the computer you are using, information about your browser and operating system, date
and time of access and the internet address and page which linked you to our web site. The staff of
IIMA uses such information to diagnose problems, to administer and improve our website and to
generate aggregate statistical reports that analyze general user information and demographics.
Unless required by legal process, we do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This
means that user sessions may be tracked by IP address, but a user's identity remains anonymous.
In addition, we ordinarily do not disclose site usage to third parties by individual IP addresses, but
may do so in very limited circumstances when complying with law or legal process, working with
consultants assisting us in fixing or improving our site, or in monitoring and improving the security of
our network. Our staff monitors search terms that users enter into our Search Engine, but this tracking
is never associated with individual users.
Cookies
Cookies are unique bits of computer data that many major websites will transfer to your computer the
first time that you visit. Cookies are stored on your hard drive and may be later accessed by the
website to track prior usage. IIMA may use cookies and pixels, or transparent GIF files. With both
cookies and Spotlight technology, the information that we collect and share is anonymous and not
personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address.

A cookie may also be used to deliver customizable and personalized services for information by
tracking already visited pages. We may also use cookies to anonymously track session information,
such as pages visited or duration of visit, which will help us continue to improve our format and
content.
You may be able to set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when one is being sent. It is
likely that some portions of our site will not operate properly if cookies are disabled.
External Links
IIMA site contains links to other independently run Web sites within our network and to some sites
outside www.iimahd.ernet.in, www.iima.edu.in & www.iima.ac.in domains that are not controlled by
IIMA and are not covered by this privacy policy. IIMA is not responsible for the privacy practices,
security or content of such Web sites.
Security Precautions
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information
under our control. Unfortunately, due to the nature of Internet communications, no data transmission
over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. While IIMA remains committed to
protecting the privacy of our users, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you
transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best
effort to ensure its security on our systems. We do so by using secure technology, privacy protection
controls, and restrictions on employee access, however, we make no representations regarding the
veracity of such measures.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with
this Website, please contact us at webrequest@iimahd.ernet.in.
